

GitHub

h1xC0

Phone

+373 79465535

Email

andreyduck24@outlook.com

EDUCATION

NETWORK TEHNICIAN

CENTER OF EXCELLENCE IN ENERGY AND ELECTRONICS

2016-2020

HARD SKILLS

UNITY 3D

Dotween, Odin Inspector, Photon, Addressables,

EXPERIENCED

C# (SOLID, GOF, LINQ)

MIDDLE

SHADERS

NOVICE

ARCHITECTURE

Zenject, MV* Frameworks, UniRx, UniTask MIDDLE

VCS

Gitflow, Git(Bitbucket, GitHub,

GitLab, Unity Collab) **EXPERIENCED**

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

UPPER-INTERMEDIATE

RUSSIAN

FLUENT

ROMANIAN

NATIVE

ADRIAN MIRON

UNITY DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Developer with a 4-year professional journey, spanning the vibrant spectrum of game development from Hyper Casual gems to high-quality AA adventures. I breathe life into games, crafting immersive experiences that captivate players across diverse platforms. Ready to push boundaries and create the next gaming sensation!

WORK EXPERIENCE

APR 2022 - PRESENT

FIVERR

UNITY DEVELOPER

- · Fixing bugs
- · Creating prototypes from scratch
- · Integrating SDK
- · Building games for Android, WebGl, PC

APR 2023 - JAN 2024

VICCON

C# DEVELOPER

- · Working on database improvements
- · Improving overall performance
- Maintained and developed new features

MAY 2022 - APR 2023

DRAGON'S LAKE

EXPERIENCED UNITY DEVELOPER

- · Working on a game and generic code
- · Analyze and improve performance across all target platforms
- · Develop new and maintain existing code base for current and future projects
- · Analyze and optimize solutions
- · Contribute original ideas towards all aspects of game production and development
- · Work independently to complete assigned projects with limited supervision
- Keep up to date with the technological developments and advancements in the computer game industry

APR 2021 - APR 2022

OURVIEW GAMES

EXPERIENCED UNITY DEVELOPER

- · Create mobile game prototypes from scratch
- Maintain a good performance and optimize projects for main platforms
- Integrate mobile SDK(such as Applovin MAX, Amplitude, etc.)

APR 2020 - APR 2021

MIDNIGHT WORKS

UNITY DEVELOPER

- Prototyping 3D games from scratch
- Programming game logic, UI and more
- · Optimizing performance for mobile devices
- · Third-party SDK integration (Facebook, GA, AdMob, etc.)
- · Building projects for iOS and Android